

Phattanothai Pukham



Personal Information

≥■Nick Name **W** Date of birth Military Status **B** Date of Availability

Fluke 3 may 1993 Reservist **Immediately**

I don't have much work experience. But I am ready to learn and develop. I'm the type of person who likes a challenge. easy to get along with I like to try new things and develop myself all the time.

I hope that we will have the opportunity to work together.

Contect

☐ Tel 0875683762 Email 5 zeref38@gmail.com **Q** Address 96 Moo.6 Tambon Thanthong, Amphur Phan, Chiang Rai 57250

Github **■** Website https://github.com/phattanotai https://portfolios.gracia.tech

Skills

Graphic De 30%		
Coding		
	90%	
Database		
	<i>80</i> %	
Server		
	70 %	
Research		
	85%	

EDUCATION

2012-2016

Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University GPA 3.21

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present

10 Nov. 2020 - 2021

Freelance Full Stack Developer Developer at OTEN INNOVAT GROUP CO.,

LTD, Chiang Mai (Remote Work)

Developer at GWT, Chiang Rai

1 Jul. 2020 - 8 Nov. 2020 1 Jul. 2019 - 30 Jun. 2020

Programmer at WORLD GPS TRACKER

LIMITED PARTNERSHIP, Chiang Rai

1 May 2018 – 30 Apr. 2019

Fort Mengraimaharaj Hospital, Chiang Rai

E ABILITIES

Coding Python, Nodejs, PHP, SQL, C/C++, C#, Java, Javascript,

Typescript

Flask, Express, Slim, Nestjs

Angular, Vue.js, React, Nextjs, React Native, Ionic, Jquery

Bootstrap, Material-ui

DevExtreme, Rxjs, Redux, Vuex

One Signal, Pusher, Selenium, Graphql, Apollo, Threejs

Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose

Google Map, Leaflet Map, Longdo Map

Polling, Server Sent Event, Websocket, SocketIO

OpenCv, EmguCV

Integrate Api e.g. dlt, scg, cpf, Integrate gamebrand e.g.

sexy, pg, sbobet send sms email, line api

Database Postgresql, Mysql, Sql Server, Mongodb, Redis, SQLite

> Config Replication Master and Slave Server Postgis, Geo, Stored Procedure, Database trigger

Server Ubuntu, Window Server, Nginx , Load Balance, Cluster

> Mode, Kubernetes, Docker, Docker Swarm, Kong Api Gateway, Cloudflare, GCP, AWS, Netlify, CircleCI,

Prometheus, Grafana, gRPC, RabbitMQ

Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github, Jira, Asana General

Researching Microservice, Microfrontend, Service Mesh Isito, Argo CD,

> Jenkins, Apache Kafka, Terraform, Ansible Elasticsearch, Opensearch, LevelDB, Firebase

Robot Framework, Cypress, Figma

Flutter, Laravel, Spring Boot, ASP.Net Core, FastAPI, Rust, Golang, Solidity, Wab3, Ethers.js, Truffle, Kotlin, Swift,

Unity, Facebook API, WebRTC